{
    "id": "32935b2129e540cd97829c9bdf630763",
    "title": "Grammar worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ace201d2cd754a39aa186c670bed9303",
            "title": "Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I don’t care …………………. your opinion. I will do what I want.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "of",
                        "about",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sorry I broke the vessel – I ………………. help it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't",
                        "couldn't",
                        "couldn't but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who takes ………………….. the sick in hospitals?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "care about",
                        "care of",
                        "care after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Janet is a selfish woman, but still I ………………….. her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't help liking",
                        "can't help like",
                        "can't help but liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am the happiest woman …………………. the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The apartment ………………… I live is very small.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "were",
                        "where",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t paid the fee. I haven’t …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither",
                        "either",
                        "also",
                        "as well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Books ………………….. all over the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "were laying",
                        "were lying",
                        "were laid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I always have trouble ………………….. phone numbers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to remember",
                        "remembering",
                        "to remembering",
                        "remember"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ....................... for six hours.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is raining",
                        "has been raining",
                        "was raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}